ABOUT ME

Creative software developer with 4 years of experience managing IT systems and one year crafting ITSM software at a small consultancy. Desire to use proven technical and communication skills to develop high quality business systems. Enthusiastic to learn new software, surmount engineering hurdles, and hunt down pesky bugs.

PROJECT

Job Scraper

Python app that scrapes Indeed for jobs according to input search terms, outputs to a CSV.

SKILLS

Languages:

Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL

Operating Systems:

Linux (Arch/Antergos), MS Windows

DevOps:

Git

Frameworks:

JUnit

IDEs/Text Editors:

VSCode, nVim

Misc:

Relational database schema, Agile methodology, VMware

ScottGreen

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | Denver, CO

AWARDS AND PUBLICATIONS

AIRMAN OF THE YEAR - 961st AACS, Kadena AB, 2010

Jackson, E. D.; Green, S. C.; Prieto, A. L. **Electrochemical Performance of Electrodeposited Zn4Sb3Films for Sodium-Ion Secondary Battery Anodes.** ACS Applied Materials & Interfaces 2015, 7 (14), 7447–7450.

WORK HISTORY

(Sep. 2017 - Sep. 2018)

ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT - T4S Partners

- Used a declarative scripting language to design multiple back-end systems, including an auto-assignment ticketing system, REST API integration, and email parsing.
- Pair programmed in an end-to-end development pipeline, with Dev., Test and Prod. servers. Coordinated testing, deployment of features, and bug fixes for a SaaS business product.
- Troubleshot production-affecting service outages. Determined causes and implemented solutions, minimizing downtime and improving client relations.

(June 2008 - June 2012)

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN - USAF | Kadena, Japan and Beale, CA

 Operated in teams composed of varied specialties to maintain two AWACS aircraft and a DCGS system.

EDUCATION

(May, 2016)

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, CHEMISTRY - Colorado State University

- Organized study groups for advanced chemistry courses. Helped improve classmate's grades from C's to A's.
- ACS certified degree with courses in organic, inorganic and physical chemistry, biochemistry, calculus-based statistics and physics.

(Sep. 2016 - August 2017)

MATERIALS SCIENCE ENGINEERING - University of Washington

Advanced coursework in semiconductor theory and design.



